#### ZAHRA ADELINIA

+989197169565 • zahra.adelinia@gmail.com • Tehran, Iran

https://www.linkedin.com/in/zahra-adelinia-852a7296/

## PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I have been in the software industry for many years from teaching to producing various softwares. My passion for modern technologies led me to focus on Javascript.

Core Competencies and Skills: JavaScript, React.js, Next.js, Typescript, React Query, Redux, Zustand, Tailwind, NPM, API, Nodejs, PostgreSQL, GitHub, HTML, CSS, Sass.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Mohanna (Tehran, Iran) - Fullstack Developer 2024 - present

Development intelligent bachelor's referral system.

– Using JavaScript, Next.js, Typescript, React Query, Zustand, Tailwind NPM, Nodejs, PostgreSQL, Rest API, Git, HTML, CSS,

SabaTamin (Tehran, Iran) - Frontend Developer 2022 - 2024

Developing front parts of the web applications in this company, most of them are about Capital Market.

Using JavaScript, React, Next.js, Typescript, React Query, Zustand, Tailwind NPM, Rest API, Git, HTML,
CSS

# Personal projects:

Dictionary app in React,

Weather app in React,

Responsive Portfolio Project and

Vanilla JS Weather Forecast

on: https://github.com/zahra-p?tab=repositories

Freelance (Tehran, Iran) 2018 – 2022

Website design and implementation

- WordPress websites

Fanzio (Tehran, Iran) – Full Stack Developer 2017 – 2018

Developing tracking system in this company, it was about controlling cars and drivers by using the data that were be sent from GPS devices which were installed on them.

- − I was customizing it either in front end and backend parts.
- Working on map with Java Script
- Using PHP and MySql

Rightel (Tehran, Iran) – Full Stack Developer 2015 – 2017

Designing and developing web chat system for Rightel company, with lots of complicated reports on registered data from chat system.

- Creating forms for admin side of the system.
- Creating complicated reports from the registered data.
- Using PHP and MySql

## Freelance Works 2009 - 2015

Information exchange system between real estate companies in the form of Client Server. – Design and development of the system

- Using Visual Basic and Sql Server E-commerce program for Dan Aver company.
- Design and development of the system
- Using Visual Basic and Sql Server Accounting and warehouse software for wholesale distribution centers.
- Design and development of the system
- Using Visual Basic and Sql Server Software for technical and vocational schools to do all things related to students.

- Design and development of the system

- Using Visual Basic and Sql Server The performance program of the examinees of the regions of

Khuzestan province for the technical and professional organization of this province.

Design and development of the system

- Using Visual Basic and Sql Server The simulator system for entrance exams in the form of four-choice

questions with time limit

Design and development of the system

- Using C++ in SQL Laboratory system for Iran Khodro company.

- Design and development of the system

Using FoxPro Data into Microsoft Access

Iran Nara (Tehran, Iran) – Software Engineer 2005 – 2009

This company provides office machines and their services, I was responsible for the check system of Sepah and Maskan banks.

Development and customization of the check book printing machine software system

- Creating complicated reports from the registered data

Using Visual Basic and Sql Server

Technical and professional organization (Khuzestan, Iran) – Teacher 2002 – 2005

More than two years of teaching in all fields in technical and vocational schools (having a coaching

Programming degree from the technical and professional organization).

**EDUCATION** 

Islamic Azad University, Tehran, Tehran – Bachelor's degree, Computer Engineering

**Licenses & certifications** 

SheCodes React: Issued Jan 2022 · No Expiration Date

SheCodes Responsive: Issued Nov 2021 · No Expiration Date

SheCodes Plus: Issued Oct 2021 · No Expiration Date